{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622685","name":"House of BBQ","address":"16619 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224","owner":null,"licenseNumber":"229392","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-82.93492,42.40441","geojson":{"id":"51622685","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-82.934919078,42.404413389]},"properties":{"name":"House of BBQ","owner":null,"address":"16619 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"229392","establishmentid":"51622685","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"5/4/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"2466","name":"Pizza Hut #26290","address":"16835 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"418","name":"East English Village Bar & Grill","address":"16915 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51622692","name":"J's Wings-N-Things","address":"12250 E Outer Drive","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51622845","name":"Flamzs","address":"16369 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"5172","name":"Danny's Diner","address":"17017 E Warren","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51622784","name":"York Sussex Partners","address":"17017 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51622709","name":"Wing Snob Detroit","address":"17101 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"2861","name":"Jeanie's Lounge","address":"16200 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"1992","name":"Domino's Pizza","address":"17140 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51622483","name":"The Detroit Pepper Company","address":"17180 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"53082","inspectionDate":"2020-10-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-501.112","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, REFUSE receptacles not meeting the requirements specified by law such as receptacles that are not rodent-resistant, unprotected plastic bags and paper bags, or baled units that contain materials with FOOD residue may not be stored outside.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored outside, unprotected","subProblem":"","location":"OUTSIDE PREMISES","subLocation":"To the left of Rear door","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-202.18","violationDescription":"Filters or other grease extracting EQUIPMENT shall be designed to be readily removable for cleaning and replacement if not designed to be cleaned in place.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation hood filter(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Grease extraction filters","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-205.10","violationDescription":"FOOD EQUIPMENT that is certified or classified for sanitation by an American National Standards Institute (ANSI)-accredited certification program is deemed to comply with Parts 4-1 and 4-2 of this chapter.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"OUTSIDE GRILL AREA","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-205.10","violationDescription":"FOOD EQUIPMENT that is certified or classified for sanitation by an American National Standards Institute (ANSI)-accredited certification program is deemed to comply with Parts 4-1 and 4-2 of this chapter.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"OUTSIDE GRILL AREA","subLocation":"At the Bar-B-Q pit / oven","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \r\n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Microwave oven door seals and cavities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Inside the Microwave Oven(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Floor mats","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"45078","inspectionDate":"2018-05-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \r\n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\r\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\r\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Beyond consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Inside the Cooler (upright)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-05-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Dispose of food item."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"chlorine","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Missing Test strips","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"seals","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Inside the Cooler (2 door)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Inside the Stove","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \r\n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Microwave oven door seals and cavities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Inside the Microwave Oven(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-10-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622685"}}